<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<contents>
	<content name="plot" text="Almost 2000 years ago, first colonial ship set sail from the Old Earth. Since then, thousands of planets have been colonized.
These colonies were founded by different types of societies: military dictatorships, democracies, various monarchies, fanatical theocracies and even corporate structures.
The colonies didn’t interact for ages, but gradual expansion of territory reached gigantic proportions and the governments started to communicate. 
Cultural exchange, science, technology and interstellar trade flourished. 
Nevertheless, human nature never changes - in close proximity conflict is unavoidable.
Human civilization gone through numerous of armed conflicts, from small borderland clashes to fierce atrocities of genocide when whole nations were eradicated.
This story is about one of these encounters, insignificant to measures of whole humanity and crucial for its participants.

The sides of the conflict:
“Devil’s Dozen” corporation is an interstellar holding. It consists of 7 planets in 5 star systems.
Mighty economics and high life standards are the top priority of the Corporation.
It is achieved by highly developed trade, professional political management and protected by top tech military fleet. 

Delanel theocracy was founded by radical religious fanatics.  
Their primary goal is to spread and impose their beliefs. 
This theocracy is known for its effective economy due to diligence and selfless patriotism and last, but not the least impetuous warmongering politics.
Theocrats have no mercy to infidels and fervently believe that bringing the light of their faith to every single corner of the Galaxy is their destiny.
"/>
	<content name="help" text="Spaceships, as well as rockets and torpedoes fired from them are controlled the same way.

Spaceship can’t fire if “rocket”, ‘torpedo’ or ‘shield’ ability is active this turn.

Beware! Asteroids are deadly for all spaceships.

Spaceship can’t use abilities if it has any active defect.
"/>
</contents>